[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The cruise liner capsizes in the disaster classic The Poseidon Adventure.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Identify the 1989 horror movie from the quote: And the timeless secrets of Osiris will once again animate the lifeless!", "correct_answer": "Puppetmaster", "incorrect_answers": ["Childs Play", "The Brain", "Warlock"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Did Joanna Cassidy play the role of Rose Lindsey in Dont Tell Mom the Babysitters Dead?", "correct_answer": "Yes", "incorrect_answers": ["No"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "If x is positive, then x^2  x.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the name of Eddie Murphys character in the 1984 comedy movie Beverly Hills Cop?", "correct_answer": "Axel Foley", "incorrect_answers": ["Douglas Todd", "Victor Maitland", "Mikey Tandino"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Jack Butler", "correct_answer": "Mr. Mom", "incorrect_answers": ["Pretty in Pink", "Class Reunion", "European Vacation"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What unusual phenomenon occurs when Snow White from the Shrek movies starts singing?", "correct_answer": "Animals appear out of nowhere.", "incorrect_answers": ["An earthquake strikes.", "She transforms into a bird.", "Flowers bloom all around her."]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This actress won The Worst Actress Razzie in 1986, 1987, 1993, 2000 and 2002.", "correct_answer": "Madonna", "incorrect_answers": ["Jessica Alba", "Amy Irving", "Jennifer Lopez"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of these European countries is not home to any wild native reindeer?", "correct_answer": "Switzerland", "incorrect_answers": ["Finland", "Russia", "Scotland"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the largest island of Canada, and the fifth-largest island in the world?", "correct_answer": "Baffin Island", "incorrect_answers": ["Victoria Island", "Banks Island", "Devon Island"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Complete this Irish saying: Dont let your ______ cut your throat.", "correct_answer": "tongue", "incorrect_answers": ["jealousy", "mother-in-law", "stale bread"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Chuck Berry recorded this song in 1972 and used to call it My Alma Mater. Mary Whitehouse, a British morality campaigner, made an unsuccessful attempt to get the song banned.", "correct_answer": "My Ding-a-Ling", "incorrect_answers": ["Johnny B. Goode", "Roll Over Beethoven", "Maybelline"]}]